Dashboard. Click Run profit scan to refresh the margin scan.
The Action center summarizes catalog health, issues to review, and inventory risk.
Click the Fix first card area to focus on the suggested minimum price and next action.
Click Export full fix list. Margin Sentinel stays read-only and never changes Shopify prices automatically.
Click a finding row to see the product that needs attention.
The row shows SKU, price, cost, margin, inventory risk, and suggested minimum price.
Click the suggested price and next-action columns to show what the merchant should do next.
This makes the scan actionable instead of just reporting a number.
Pricing page. Click each plan to show what the merchant gets.
Free includes a small scan and CSV export. Starter unlocks larger scans, supplier import, what-if, and alerts.
Growth is for bigger catalogs and priority support.
Click Start 14-day trial. Paid plans are handled through Shopify billing.
Supplier import. Click the CSV area to show the accepted columns: variant ID, inventory item ID, SKU, and cost.
Click the matched count. The preview confirms which rows match Shopify variants before saving.
Click the What-if controls to model supplier cost increases.
This helps merchants respond before low-margin products continue selling.
Export. Click Download findings CSV to create the saved fix list.
The CSV includes issue type, product, cost source, margin gap, inventory risk, and next action.
Actionable next steps are clear: raise price, reduce cost, fix missing cost, or review discount rules.
That is the core promise: catch margin leaks before products keep selling.